Graf, Oskar Marie; Papers ger002
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf, 1920-1985; 2; 149 file folders
  - Correspondence with contemporaries, publishers, 2.2
    - George, Manfred, 1939; 1958 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 51)
    - Gerson, Tove, 1963-1967; 1974-1979 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 52)
    - Grass, Günter, 1963-1966 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 53)
    - Grosshut, Friedrich Sally, 1962 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 54)
    - Grünberg, Isabella, 1937 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 55)
    - Günther, Joachim (Sigbert Mohn Verlag), 1964-1965 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 56)
    - Guttenbrunner, Michael, 1958-1966 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 57)
    - Habe, Hans, 1965 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 58)
    - [Haftel], Eugen, 1963-1964 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 59)
    - Hardt, Ludwig, 1938 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 60)
    - Hartung, Hugo, 1946-1968; 1972 (death notice) (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 61)
    - Heine, Th. Th, 1933-1935 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 62)
    - Held, Hans Ludwig, 1963 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 63)
    - Herzfelde, Wieland, 1949; 1963 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 64)
    - Hesse, Hermann, 1946-1971 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 65)
    - Heuss, Theodor, 1954; Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 66)
    - Hindemith, Paul, 1945 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 67)
    - Hochhuth, Rolf, 1963 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 68)
    - Hoegner, Wilhelm, 1945-1953 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 69)
    - Höllriegel, Arnold, 1938 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 70)
    - Hofheinz, E., 1967 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 71)
    - Hohenemser, Herbert, 1964 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 72)
    - Horvath, Ödon, [1933] (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 73)
    - Howell, Soskin, Publishers, Inc., 1940-1943 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 74)
    - Ja-Press (Zürich), 1967 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 75)
    - Jens, Walter, 1963-1964; 1975-1976 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 76)
    - Jung, Franz, 1961 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 77)
    - Keprda, Franz, 1946-1966; 1978-1984 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 78)
    - Knoeringen, Waldemar von, 1964 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 79)
    - Kohn, Hein, 1954-1963; 1970-1974 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 80)
    - Kolmsperger, Max, 1963; 1969; 1977 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 81)
      Kolmsperger, Anna.
    - Leiser, Erwin, 1962 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 82)
    - Liepman, Ruth, 1966; 1980 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 83)
    - Lips, Julius, 1928 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 84)
    - Loewenstein, Prinz Hubertus zu, 1934-1946 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 85)
    - Lowe, Ruth Norden, 1964 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 86)
    - Luitpold, Josef, 1963-1964 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 87)
    - Mann, Erika, 1938 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 88)
    - Mann, Heinrich, 1936-1948 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 89)
    - Mann, Katja, 1955-1965; 1970-1975 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 90)
    - Mann, Klaus, 1933-1939 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 91)
    - Mann, Thomas, 1938-1955 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 92)
    - Manschinger, Kurt & Elisabeth, 1938-1959 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 93)
    - Marcuse, Ludwig, 1954 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 94)
    - Meckauer, Walter, 1958 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 95)
    - Meyer, Heinrich, 1967 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 96)
    - Michäelis, Karin, 1943 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 97)
    - Mileck, Joseph, 1964-1965 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 98)
    - Minder, Robert, 1966-1967; 1980 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 99)
    - Mitterer, Erika, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 100)
    - Müller, Erich, 1947 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 101)
    - Muschg, Walter, 1965 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 102)
    - Nabold, Fritz (Nest-Verlag), 1965-1966 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 103)
    - Neumann, Alfred, Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 104)
    - Neumann, Robert, 1963 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 105)
    - Niederland, Dr, 1954 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 106)
    - Olden, Rudolf, 1933-1938 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 107)
    - "Open Letter to His Holiness, Pope Paul VI", 1965 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 108)
    - P.E.N. Club (Rudolf Olden, Hans Martin Elster, Ödon Horvath, Johannes Tralow), 1933-1951 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 109)
    - Penzoldt, Ernst, 1949 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 109a)
    - Pfeiler, William K., 1960 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 110)
    - Preminger, Otto, 1961 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 111)
    - Recknagel, Rolf, 1967; 1969-1985 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 112)
    - Reet, Marion, 1959 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 113)
    - Reichsstelle für Förderung des deutschen Schrifttums (Nazi), 1933 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 114)
    - Remarque, Erich Maria, 1963-1964 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 115)
    - Renn, Ludwig, 1942 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 116)
    - Rilke, Rainer Maria, 1919 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 117)
    - Roda Roda, Alexander, Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 118)
    - Rosenwald, Kurt, 1933-1958 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 119)
    - Schaber, Will, 1963-1967; 1973-1985 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 120)
    - Scharoun, President, Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 121)
    - Schmidt, Eugen, 1951 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 122)
    - Schoeller, Wilfried F., 1966; 1974-1981 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 123)
      Schoeller, Reinhild.
    - Schröder-Kiewert, Walter, 1947-1960 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 124)
    - Schütte, Ernst, 1965-1967; 1971 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 125)
    - Schutzverband deutscher Schriftsteller (SDS), 1933 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 126)
    - Stone, Judy, 1967 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 127)
    - Thompson, Dorothy, 1938 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 128)
    - Tietz, Josef, 1960-1964 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 129)
    - Tretiakov (Tretjakov), Sergei & Olga, 1934-1937 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 130)
    - Unruh, Fritz von, 1949; 1955 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 131)
    - Verlag Kurt Desch, 1947-1967 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 132)
    - Viertel, Berthold, 1939 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 133)
    - Vogel, Hans-Jochen, 1966; 1970-1975 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 134)
    - Voigt, Rudolf, published, 1945-1953 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 135)
    - von der Heydt, 1963; 1968 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 136)
    - Wach, Oscar, 1955-1958 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 137)
    - Waldinger, Ernst, 1947-1967 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 138)
    - Waldo, Hilde, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 139)
    - Warnecke, Robert, 1931; transcript (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 140)
    - Wilhelm, Kurt, 1966-1967 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 141)
    - Wilkie, Wendell L., 1944 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 142)
    - Wulff, Catalina W. de, 1948; 1958 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 143)
    - Birthday greetings, Undated (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 144)
    - Publishers, newspapers, 1920-1966 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 145)
    - Radio and television stations, 1964-1967 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 146)
    - Miscellaneous, 1927-1967 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence of Oskar Maria Graf), Folder 147)
- Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf, 1967-1987; 3; 107 file folders
  The Gisela Graf correspondence files date predominately from the time of her husband's death until 1986. It is a mixture of originals, carbons and photocopies; much of the correspondence deals with the posthumous publication of her husband's works and exhibitions concerning his life and career. Correspondents include: Jean Améry, Günther Anders, Eric Bentley, Ernst Bloch, Hilde Domin, Walter and Anne-Marie Fabian, Erich Fromm, Helmut Hirsch, Uwe Johnson, Mascha Kaléko, Alfred Kantorowicz, Hermann Kesten, Annemarie Koch (Graf's daughter by his first marriage), Ernst Lothar, Helmut Pfanner and the University of New Hampshire, Johannes and Gertrude Urzidil, Walter Wicclair, and Carl Zuckmayer.
  - A, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 148)
  - Aicher-Scholl, Inge, 1978 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 149)
  - Aigner, Bruno, 1977-1978 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 150)
  - Akademie der Künste, Berlin (Walther Huder), 1967-1986 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 151)
  - Améry, Jean, 1976-1977 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 152)
  - Anders, Günther, 1971 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 153)
  - Andersch, Alfred, Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 154)
  - B, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 155)
  - Bauer, Gerhard, 1981-1989 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 156)
  - Bayerische Staatsbibliothek, Munich, 1968-1987 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 157)
  - Becher, Ulrich, 1979 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 158)
  - Bentley, Eric, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 159)
  - Bittner-Simmet, Magda, 1977-1978 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 160)
  - Bloch, Ernst, 1975-1976 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 161)
  - Brainin, Fritz, 1980 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 162)
  - Brandt, Willy, 1978 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 163)
  - Büchergilde Gutenberg, 1969-1986 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 164)
  - Burger, Eric (Internationaler Schutzverband deutschsprachiger Schriftsteller, ISDS), 1978-1979 (Box 2 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 165)
  - C, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 2 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 166)
  - D, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 1)
  - Die Deutsche Bibliothek (Brita Eckert, Werner Berthold), 1972-1979 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 2)
  - Dollinger, Hans (Süddeutscher Verlag), 1967-1980 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 3)
  - Dollinger, Hans (Süddeutscher Verlag), 1981-1991 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 4)
  - Domin, Hilde, 1976; 1978 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 5)
  - E, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 6)
  - F, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 7)
  - Fabian, Walter & Anne-Marie, 1974-1980 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 8)
  - Floch, Toni, 1978-1981 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 9)
  - Frank, Charlott, 1968-1973 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 10)
  - Fromm, Erich, 1964 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 11)
  - G, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 12)
  - Guggenheim, Felix, 1968 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 13)
  - H, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 14)
  - Hans, Jan, 1976 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 15)
  - Hartung, Sigyn, 1972-1977 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 16)
  - Heintz, Georg, 1976-1977 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 17)
  - Hertin, Paul W., 1972-1982 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 18)
  - Hirsch, Helmut, 1980 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 19)
  - Homann, Ursula, 1987 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 20)
  - Huntington, Isa, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 21)
  - I, J, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 22)
  - Johnson, Uwe, 1975 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 23)
  - K, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 24)
  - Kaléko, Mascha, 1974 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 25)
  - Kantorowicz, Alfred, 1974-1975 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 26)
  - Kaufmann, Ulrich, 1977-1980 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 27)
  - Kesten, Hermann, 1974-1976 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 28)
  - Kirsten, Wulf, 1978-1981 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 29)
  - Koch, Annemarie (Graf's daughter), 1976-1991 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 30)
  - L, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 31)
  - Lamm, Hans, 1969 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 32)
  - Lothar, Ernst, 1968 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 33)
  - M, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 34)
  - Marks, Helen, 1968-1969 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 35)
  - Metzdorf, Robert, 1968 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 36)
  - Meyer, Heinrich, 1969 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 37)
  - Mierendorff, Marta, 1974-1980 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 38)
  - Morton, Frederic, 1979 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 39)
  - Müller, Franz, 1969 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 40)
  - N, O, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 41)
  - Noel, Camillo, 1968-1969 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 42)
  - Ostfeld, Leo, 1966-1979 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 43)
  - P, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 44)
  - Pfanner, Helmut F., 1967-1986 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 45)
  - Pinthus, Kurt, 1968-1973 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 46)
  - R, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 47)
  - Ramsauer, Ulrike, 1982-1986 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 48)
  - S, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 49)
  - Stein, Liselotte, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 50)
  - T, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 51)
  - U, V, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 52)
  - University of New Hampshire, 1870-1981 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 53)
  - University of New Hampshire, 1983-1988 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 54)
  - Urzidil, Johannes & Gertrude, 1969 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 55)
  - Verlag Kurt Desch, 1967-1971 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 56)
  - Verlag Kurt Desch, 1972-1977 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 57)
  - Verlag Kurt Desch. Royalty statements, 1968-1975 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 58)
  - Verlag Kurt Desch, Undated; clippings (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 59)
  - W, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 60)
  - Walser, Martin, 1975-1976 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 61)
  - Walter, Hans-Albert, 1972-1980 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 62)
  - Wartenberg, Carla, 1978-1981 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 63)
  - Wicclair, Walter, 1974 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 64)
  - Wiesner, Annemarie, 1978-1979 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 65)
  - Wronkow, Ludwig, 1977 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 66)
  - Z, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 67)
  - Zimmermann, Hanns, 1969-1974 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 68)
  - Zuckmayer, Carl, 1974-1976 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 69)
  - Unidentified, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 70)
  - Condolence letters, 1967-1968 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 71)
  - Graf's grave site in Munich, 1967-1980 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 72)
  - Graf's 80th birthday, 1974 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 73)
  - 10th anniversary of Graf's death, 1977 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 74)
  - 20th anniversary of Graf's death, 1987 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 75)
  - Exhibits, Europe, Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 76)
  - Exhibits, U.S., Undated (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 77)
  - Newspapers, 1967-1978 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 78)
  - Ph.D. and M.A. candidates, 1967-1985 (Box 3 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 79)
  - Publishers, literary agents, 1967-1975 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 1)
  - Publishers, literary agents, 1976-1979 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 2)
  - Publishers, literary agents, 1980-1990 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 3)
  - Radio and television stations, 1967-1979 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 4)
  - Radio and television stations, 1980-1991 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 5)
  - Radio and television stations, undated and letter fragments (Box 4 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 6)
  - Records (Schallplatten) of Oskar Maria Graf, 1967-1972 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 7)
  - Verwerfungsgesellschaft WORT, 1975-1981 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 8)
  - Zeitungs-Ausschnitt-Büro, 1966-1981 (Box 4 (3-Correspondence of Gisela Blauner Graf), Folder 9)
- Published and unpublished writings of Oskar Maria Graf, 1919-1967; 4; 378 file folders
  This series contains copies of Graf's published and unpublished writings, either in typescript or published form. The novels and story collections are listed first, followed by unpublished longer works, essays and short stories, and miscellaneous other pieces last. The series contains a mixture of original and carbon typescripts, clippings of published writings, and reviews of the individual works.
  - Published novels, short story collections, 1919-1989; 4.1
    - Der Abgrund, 1935 (Box 4 (4-Published and unpublished writings of Oskar Maria ), Folder 10)
      Photocopy of published book with corrections, pp. 1-200.
    - Der Abgrund, pp. 201-400, Undated (Box 4 (4-Published and unpublished writings of Oskar Maria ), Folder 11)
    - Der Abgrund, pp. 401-end, Undated (Box 4 (4-Published and unpublished writings of Oskar Maria ), Folder 12)
    - Der Abgrund .Changes to text, Undated (Box 4 (4-Published and unpublished writings of Oskar Maria ), Folder 13)
    - Der Abgrund / The Abyss, Undated (Box 4 (4-Published and unpublished writings of Oskar Maria ), Folder 14)
      Reviews, critiques.
    - Altmodische Gedichte eines Dutzendmenschen, 1962 (Box 4 (4-Published and unpublished writings of Oskar Maria ), Folder 15)
      Reviews.
    - Amen und Anfang, 1919 (Box 4 (4-Published and unpublished writings of Oskar Maria ), Folder 16)
    - An manchen Tagen (1985).Reviews, Undated (Box 4 (4-Published and unpublished writings of Oskar Maria ), Folder 17)
    - An manchen Tagen: "Verbrennt mich!" (p. 14), Undated; typescript (Box 4 (4-Published and unpublished writings of Oskar Maria ), Folder 18)
    - An manchen Tagen: "Dem Andenken Ludwig Thoma" (p. 48), Undated (Box 4 (4-Published and unpublished writings of Oskar Maria ), Folder 19)
      Typescript, reviews.
    - An manchen Tagen :"Etwas über den Bayrischen Humor" (p. 76), Undated; typescripts, clippings (Box 4 (4-Published and unpublished writings of Oskar Maria ), Folder 20)
    - An manchen Tagen: "Erste Begegnung mit Schiller"/"In Honor of Schiller" (p. 126), Undated (Box 4 (4-Published and unpublished writings of Oskar Maria ), Folder 21)
      Clipping of German version, typescript of English version.
    - An manchen Tagen: "Über das wesentliche Lesen" (p. 168), Undated; typescript, clippings (Box 4 (4-Published and unpublished writings of Oskar Maria ), Folder 22)
    - An manchen Tagen: "Rainer Maria Rilke und die Frauen" (p. 172), Undated (Box 4 (4-Published and unpublished writings of Oskar Maria ), Folder 23)
      Typescript of English translation.
    - An manchen Tagen: "Totenrede für Joseph Scharl" (p. 278), Undated; typescript (Box 4 (4-Published and unpublished writings of Oskar Maria ), Folder 24)
    - An manchen Tagen: "Nachruf auf Theodore Dreiser" (p. 282), Undated; typescript (Box 4 (4-Published and unpublished writings of Oskar Maria ), Folder 25)
    - An manchen Tagen: "Zum Tode Martin Anderson-Nexoös" (p. 285), Undated; typescript (Box 4 (4-Published and unpublished writings of Oskar Maria ), Folder 26)
    - An manchen Tagen: "Briefwechsel anlässlich seines 76. Geburtstages" (p. 289), Undated (Box 4 (4-Published and unpublished writings of Oskar Maria ), Folder 27)
      Typescript of letter to Thomas Mann.
    - An manchen Tagen: "Meine Familie und Amerika"/"My Family and America" (p. 321), Undated (Box 4 (4-Published and unpublished writings of Oskar Maria ), Folder 28)
      Typescripts of German and English versions.